Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
- Volume XVIII, issued 1921
  - 4. Admission to Harvard College and the Harvard Engineering School, 1921, second edition, February 3, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 5. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1921-1922, February 10, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 6. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1919-1920, February 25, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 7. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1919-1920, March 3, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 36)
  - 8. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1921, March 10, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 9. Summer courses in physical education, 1921, March 15, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 10. The Divinity School, 1921-1922, March 18, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 11. Information for students who intend to enter the freshman class in Harvard College in 1921, description of freshman halls, 1921, March 21, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 12. The Law School, 1921-1922, March 24, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 13. Reports of the President and of the Departments of Harvard University, 1919-1920,1921 (HU 75.25 Box 36)
    Lacking cover.
  - 14. The Dental School, 1920-1921, March 31, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 15. The Harvard Engineering School, 1921-1922, April 4, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 16. Department of Social Ethics, 1921-1922, April 7, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 16 Supplement, Department of Social Ethics, April 7, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 37)
  - 17. Summer School of Theology, 1921, April 11, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 18. Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1921, courses in education, April 14, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 19. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1921-1922, April 18, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 20. Division of History, Government and Economics, 1921-1922, April 21, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 21. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1921-1922, first edition, April 25, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 22. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1921-1922, April 28, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 23. Division of Medical Sciences, 1920-1921, May 5, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 24. Division of Mathematics, 1921-1922, May 10, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 25. Division of Chemistry, 1921-1922, May 12, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 26. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures,1921-1922, May 16, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 27. Division of the Fine Arts, 1921-1922, May 19, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 28. Graduate School of Education, 1921-1922, May 22, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 29. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics with the courses in astronomy and the Department of Engineering Sciences, 1921-1922, May 26, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 30. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1921-1922, May 31, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 31. Faculty of Architecture, School of Landscape Architecture, 1921-1922, July 1, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 32. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1921-1922,July 5, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 33. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1921-1922, second edition, July 20, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 34. Department of English, 1921-1922, July 21, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 35. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1921-1922, July 22, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 36. Department of Botany, 1921-1922, July 25, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 37. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1921-1922, July 26, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 38. Rules relating to College studies, 1921-1922, July 27, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 39. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1921-1922, July 28, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 40. Division of Anthropology, 1921-1922, July 29, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 41. Graduate School of Business Administration, rank list for 1920-1921, August 15, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 42. Rank list for 1920-1921, August 22, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 38)
  - 43. Division of Semitic Languages and History, 1921-1922, August 25, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 44. Division of Music, 1921-1922, August 30, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 45. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1921-1922, third edition, September 8, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 46. Harvard University, general information concerning Harvard College and the other departments of instruction, September 26, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
  - 49. The Harvard Medical School, 1921-1922, with an announcement of 1922-1923, October 31, 1921 (HU 75.25 Box 39)
- Volume XIX, issued 1922
  No. 44 and No. 46 were never printed.
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 1. President's report, 1920-1921; No. 2. Treasurer's statement, 1920-1921; No. 31. Laboratory of physics; No. 47. Descriptive catalogue, 1922-1923; and No. 48. Admission, Harvard College and Engineering School, 1923, December 28, 1922.
  - 3. Harvard University, general information concerning Harvard College and the other departments of instruction, second edition, January 31, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 4. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1922-1923, February 15, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 5. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1920-1921, February 24, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 38)
  - 6. Summer courses in physical education, 1922, February 28, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 7. Information for students who intend to enter the freshman class of Harvard College in 1922, description of the freshman halls, March 7, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 8. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1922, March 14, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 9. The Dental School, 1921-1922, March 16, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 10. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1922-1923,March 20, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 11. Bussey Institution for Research in Applied Biology, 1922, March 22, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 12. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1922-1923, March 24, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 13. The Law School, 1922-1923, March 27, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 14. Department of Social Ethics, 1922-1923, March 30, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 15. General expenses and College aids in Harvard College, the Harvard Engineering School, and the Graduate School of Applied Arts and Sciences, 1922, April 4, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 16. Division of the Fine Arts, 1922-1923, April 10, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 17. The Division of Anthropology, 1922-1923, April 14, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 18. The Divinity School, 1922-1923, April 18, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 19. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1922-1923, April 20, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 20. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1922-1923, first edition, April 24, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 21. Graduate School of Education, 1922-1923, April 26, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 22. The Harvard School of Public Health, 1922-1923, April 29, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 23. Division of Mathematics, 1922-1923, May 3, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 24. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics with the courses in astronomy and the Department of Engineering Sciences, 1922-1923, May 10, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 25. Division of Chemistry, 1922-1923, May 15, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 26. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1922-1923, May 18, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 27. The Harvard Engineering School, 1922-1923, May 22, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 28. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1922-1923, May 25, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 29. The technique and history of the drama, Department of English, departmental and allied courses in the drama, the Belmont Theatre Prize, the 47 Workshop, the Harvard Dramatic Club, the Theatre Collection, 1922-1923, May 29, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 30. Department of Zoology, 1922-1923,May 31, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 32. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1922-1923, June 12, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 33. Courses for graduates, announcement of the School of Tropical Medicine, Harvard Medical School, 1922-1923, June 15, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 34. Department of English, 1922-1923, June 19, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 35. Description of voluntary courses offered at the Harvard Medical School, 1922-1923, June 22, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 36. Courses in industrial hygiene, Harvard School of Public Health, 1922-1923, June 26, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 37. Faculty of Architecture, School of Landscape Architecture, 1922-1923, June 28, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 37 supplement. Harvard University, School of Landscape Architecture Library, a brief list of books suggested for reading and study, June 28, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 38. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1922-1923, June 30, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 39. Rules relating to College studies, 1922-1923, July 17, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 40. Graduate School of Business Administration, rank list for 1921-1922, July 24, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 41. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1922-1923, July 31, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 42. Rank list for 1921-1922, August 22, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 43. The Harvard Medical School, 1922-1923, with an announcement for 1923-1924, August 24, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
  - 45. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1922-1923, second edition, September 18, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 41)
- Volume XX, issued 1923
  Nos. 32-33, Nos. 35-40, and No. 43 were never printed.
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 2. The Dental School, 1922-1923, January 22, 1923; No. 3. Summer courses, physical education, 1923, January 24, 1923; Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction, February 12, 1923; No. 4. School of Public Health, 1922-1923, February 12, 1923; No. 6. Reports of the President and Treasurer; No. 8. Graduate School; No. 9. Division of Music, 1923-1924, March 14, 1923; No. 10. Announcement, Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1923, March 20, 1923; No. 11. The Law School, 1923-1924, March 24, 1923; No. 12. Information for students who intend to enter the freshman class of Harvard College in 1923, description of the freshman halls, March 25, 1923; No. 47. Descriptive catalogue, 1923-1924; and No. 49. Harvard University catalogue, 1923-1924.
  - 1. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1921-1922, January 16, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 40)
  - 5. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1923, February 19, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 6. The Harvard Engineering School, 1923-1924, March 6, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 13. Department of Social Ethics, 1923-1924, March 28, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 14. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1923-1924, March 30, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 15. Graduate School of Education, 1923-1924, April 2, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 16. The Theological School formed by the affiliation of the Harvard Divinity School and Andover Theological Seminary, 1923-1924, April 9, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 17. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, 1923-1924, April 12, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 18. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1923-1924, April 16, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 19. Division of the Fine Arts, 1923-1924, April 18, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 20. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1923-1924, first edition, April 23, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
    Scope and contente
    Courses, Harvard Medical School, 1923-1924, inserted, April 23, 1923.
  - 21. Division of Anthropology, 1923-1924, April 26, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 22. Division of Chemistry, 1923-1924, April 30, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 23. Division of Mathematics, 1923-1924, May 3, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 24. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics with the courses in astronomy and the Department of Engineering Sciences, 1923-1924, May 7, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 25. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1923-1924, May 10, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 26. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1923-1924, May 14, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 27. General expenses and College aids in Harvard College, the Harvard Engineering School, and the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1923, May 17, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 28. Harvard University, general information concerning Harvard College and the other departments of instruction, third edition, May 21, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 29. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1923-1924, May 24, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 30. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1923-1924, May 28, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 31. Department of English, 1923-1924, June 11, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 34. Faculty of Architecture, School of Landscape Architecture, 1923-1924, June 30, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 35. Graduate School of Business Administration, rank list for 1922-1923, July 9, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 36. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1923-1924, July 12, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 37. Rules relating to College studies, 1923-1924, July 16, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 41. Department of Military Science, 1923-1924, July 31, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 42. Rank list for 1922-1923, August 15, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 44. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1923-1924, second edition, September 17, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 45. The technique and history of the drama, Department of English, departmental and allied courses in the drama, the Belmont Theatre Prize, the 47 Workshop, the Harvard Dramatic Club, the Theatre Collection, 1923-1924, September 25, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 46. The Harvard Medical School, 1923-1924, with an announcement for 1924-1925, October 30, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 48. The Dental School, 1923-1924, November 27, 1923 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
- Volume XXI, issued 1924
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 40. Harvard University catalogue, 1924-1925.
  - 1. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1922-1923, January 14, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 2. Summer courses in physical education, 1924, January 22, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 3. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, the Harvard Engineering School, and the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, September 1924, January 31, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 4. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1924-1925, February 11, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 5. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1924, February 20, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 6. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1922-1923, February 29, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 42)
  - 7. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1924, March 13, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 8. The Harvard Engineering School, 1924-1925,March 12, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 9. Admission to Harvard College and the Harvard Engineering School, 1924, March 14, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 10. Division of Semitic Languages and History, 1924-1925, March 17, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 11. The Theological School formed by the affiliation of the Harvard Divinity School and Andover Theological Seminary, 1924-1925, March 24, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 12. Information for students who intend to enter the freshman class in Harvard College in 1924, description of the freshman halls, March 26, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 13. The Law School, 1924-1925, March 29, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 14. Division of Music, 1924-1925, March 31, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 15. The Harvard School of Public Health, 1924-1925, April 2, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 16. Division of Anthropology, 1924-1925, April 7, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 17. Division of Mathematics, 1924-1925, April 10, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 18. Department of Social Ethics, 1924-1925, April 14, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 19. Graduate School of Education, 1924-1925, April 17, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 20. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1924-1925, first edition, April 21, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 21. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, 1924-1925, April 23, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 22. Division of History, Government and Economics, 1924-1925, April 30, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 23. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1924-1925, May 8, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 24. Division of the Fine Arts, 1924-1925, May 14, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 25. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1924-1925, May 16, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 26. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1924-1925, May 19, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 27. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics with the courses in astronomy and the Department of Engineering Sciences, 1924-1925, May 22, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 28. Faculty of Architecture, School of Landscape Architecture, 1924-1925, June 16, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 29. Department of English, 1924-1925, June 14, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 30. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1924-1925, June 23, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 31. Division of Biology, Department of Botany, Department of Zoology, 1924-1925, June 30, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 32. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1924-1925, July 15, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 33. Rules relating to College studies, 1924-1925, July 28, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 34. Description of voluntary courses offered at the Harvard Medical School, 1924-1925, July 30, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 35. Division of Chemistry, 1924-1925, July 31, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 36. Rank list for 1923-1924, August 11, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 37. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1924-1925, second edition, September 15, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 38. The Harvard Medical School, 1924-1925, with an announcement for 1925-1926, October 27, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 39. The Dental School, 1924-1925, December 29, 1924 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
- Volume XXII, issued 1925
  Nos. 25 and 40 were never printed.
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 1. Statement of the treasurer, 1923-1924 and No. 4. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction, 1925-1926.
  - 2. Harvard University, general information concerning Harvard College and the other departments of instruction, fourth edition, January 26, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 3. Admission to Harvard College and the Harvard Engineering School, 1925, January 24, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 5. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1923-1924, February 24, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 43)
  - 6. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1924-1925, second edition, February 26, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 7. Summer courses in physical education, 1925, March 3, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 8. A nnouncement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1925, March 9, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 9. Information for students who intend to enter the freshman class in Harvard College in 1925, description of the freshman halls, March 12, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 10. The Theological School, formed by the affiliation of the Harvard Divinity School and Andover Theological Seminary, 1925-1926, March 16, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 11. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1925-1926, March 19, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 12. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1925, March 24, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 13. The Law School, 1925-1926, March 26, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 14. The Harvard Engineering School, 1925-1926, March 31, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 15. Rules relating to College studies, 1925, April 1, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
    Misnumbered as 6.
  - 16. Department of Social Ethics, 1925-1926, April 7, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 17. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, 1925-1926, April 8, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 18. Division of Anthropology, 1925-1926, April 18, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
    Misnumbered as 14.
  - 19. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics with the courses in astronomy and the Department of Engineering Sciences, 1925-1926, April 16, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 20. The Harvard School of Public Health, 1925-1926, April 20, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 21. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1925-1926, first edition, April 27, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 22. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, the Harvard Engineering School, and the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1925, April 30, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 23. Graduate School of Education, 1925-1926, May 5, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 24. Division of the Fine Arts, 1925-1296, May 11, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 26. Division of Mathematics, 1925-1926, May 14, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 27. Bussey Institution for Research in Applied Biology, 1925, May 22, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 28. Division of History, Government and Economics, 1925-1926, May 25, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 29. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1925-1926, May 27, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 30. Faculty of Architecture, School of Landscape Architecture, 1925-1926, May 24, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 31. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1925-1926, June 15, 1926 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 32. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1925-1926, June 16, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 33. Department of English, 1925-1926, June 22, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 34. The Harvard Engineering School, 1925-1296, second edition, July 15, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 35. Graduate School of Business Administration, rank list for 1924-1925, July 29, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 36. Description of opportunities for voluntary work offered at the Harvard Medical School, 1925-1926, August 5, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 37. Rank list for 1924-1925, August 12, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 38. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1925-1926, August 19, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 39. Division of Chemistry, 1925-1926, August 31, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 41. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1925-1926, second edition, September 21, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 42. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1925-1926, preliminary edition, October 26, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 43. The Dental School, 1925-1926, October 24, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
  - 44. The Harvard Medical School, 1925-1926, with an announcement for 1926-1927, November 18, 1925 (HU 75.25 Box 45)
- Volume XXIII, issued 1926
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 1. Statement of the Treasurer, 1924-1925 and No. 42. Harvard University catalogue, 1926-1927.
  - 2. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1924-1925, January 20, 1926 (HU 75.25 Box 44)
  - 3. Graduate School of Business Administration, February 23, 1926 (HU 75.25 Box 46)
    Misnumbered as 13.